Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
THE APARTMENT JOB
I haven't introduced myself properly.
I'm the president of Taesan Construction.
Lee Chung-won.
You seem to be great at finding things.
so what are you looking for here
at Taesan Group?
Whatever it is. I'm afraid
you won't be able to find it here.
I feel sorry about that.
No. I've already found it.
You have control
over True Value's reserve fund.
Come on.
What do you mean?
You got rid of President Seo.
so you're making it difficult
for me to use my own money.
I know I shouldn't.
but I'm starting to resent you.
The moment I treat him like an enemy.
the reserve fund goes out the window.
Then can't I just do
what President Seo used to do?
Why don't you
let me become your right-hand man?
My right-hand man?
I'm quite competent.
Of course.
You became the president
by planting relics.
Your planning. execution. and acting…
I know how impressive you are.
I'll be better than President Seo.
President Seo was the keeper of my vault.
Deposits. withdrawals.
and moving money around.
My keeper only has one job.
To keep my money safe.
That's
it?
But it's not an easy job.
This place
is filled with parasites
eating away at my fund.
They're always asking for things.
Why don't you give me a chance first.
then decide?
How would I trust you?
You came to empty out my vault.
I only realized today
that the vault had an owner.
And if there's an owner.
I should suck up to them
if I want to get any scraps.
Okay. Then do as you like.
I need to like you
to be able to trust you with my key.
I don't work with just anyone.
I can't believe the president here
was the penthouse jerk.
You used to say you admired him.
Taesan Construction really is huge.
Just wait and see how I take that key.
THE APARTMENT JOB
It's past dinnertime.
but no one's home yet.
Preparing meals wasn't in my contract.
Darn it.
I can't believe I'm doing this at my age.
Hey. come and eat!
Okay!
You're full of energy after your nap.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy.
His wife?
Why are you the president's wife?
What the hell have you been up to?
Ha-jeong. just calm down.
Mr. Park is actually my client--
Client?
This won't do.
I'm going to take this up
with your law firm.
You didn't take the bar exam
to pretend to be someone's mom.
Why would they waste
your talent like this?
Come on. I'll go talk to them.
No. Ha-jeong.
Come on. Hurry up.
Ha-jeong.
Ha-jeong…
I'm not a lawyer.
What are you talking about?
You're not a lawyer?
Let's go.
I'm not.
Kang Ha-ri.
What are you. if you're not a lawyer?
What are you. then?
Tell me! What are you?
Mom… I mean. Ha-ri. Come and eat.
Geez.
Your father-in-law
prepared dinner for you.
At least pretend to have a bite.
I don't have an appetite. Eat without me.
Then just come
and have some eggs at least…
Hey. you shouldn't have eaten
all that by yourself.
Protein is important for growing children.
Fine. Eat.
You're not eating any soup. are you?
The smell.
I'm going home.
Get home safely.
Lizard. did something happen to her?
I don't know. She's been like that
ever since picking up the kid.
See that sunken spot on the sofa?
She sat there all day.
blankly staring out the window.
Gyeong-buk.
is something going on with her?
She just needs time to herself sometimes.
Don't you even know that?
If he knew.
he wouldn't be all alone. would he?
Gyeong-buk's all grown up.
Where are you. Yeong-ju?
I opened a can since I was so frustrated.
You'd better come before I'm done.
A stand-in service?
You're joking. right?
That can't be true.
I was given a job to play the role
of Park Hae-kang's wife.
How…
-How…
-Ha-jeong.
How could you deceive me like this?
I worked so hard
to help you become a lawyer.
How could you do this to me?
I never asked you to!
Just stop.
I'm sick of hearing you say that!
Don't do anything anymore.
I know it's hard for you.
so just don't do anything for me anymore!
You're the worst.
You're so shameless.
You're…
seriously messed up.
Ms. Kang.
Were you crying?
Mr. Park.
My sister practically raised me.
I thought that was only natural.
but it feels like a luxury to me now.
I have a debt like that too.
There's someone
who took me in and protected me
instead of my father.
He…
doesn't want anything in return.
but I still want to repay him.
It's not because I feel indebted.
but because I'm grateful.
It was heartwarming.
However.
do you know that such debts
sometimes give us the motivation to go on?
You're right.
But now.
I'm not even sure if my dream
is actually mine
or my sister's.
My failure feels like
my sister's failure now.
Isn't it okay to fail?
Why should I fail?
Some things grow clearer when you fail.
You sometimes see things
that you weren't able to see before.
Then what did you see after failing?
People.
The people who are protecting me.
and the people I should protect.
So you should take a look
at what you see after failing too.
Why are you suddenly sounding so cool?
YEONG-JU
Oh. right. Yeong-ju!
What do I do?
SEOUL JUNGBU DETENTION CENTER
Inmate No. 3417. Park Yong-man.
is in the infirmary.
No visitors are allowed
due to health reasons.
MR. SON. SEOUL POLICE CHIEF
You asshole. Have you lost your mind?
How dare you come here?
Release Yong-man on medical bail first.
-The money will be ready soon.
-It doesn't work that way.
Bring the money first!
He's sick!
The elderly are always sick.
If anything happens to him.
you won't get your ten billion.
Are you out of your mind?
How dare you threaten me like that?
Are you acting like a thug again?
Damn it.
You little brat.
Mr. Park.
Park Hae-kang.
Get a grip.
I can't get him released.
But I'll let him get treatment outside.
Anything else
will be discussed
after you bring the money.
The invisible hand is the president
of the construction company?
He's something else.
He's taking money
from the apartment complex that he built?
How creative.
But shouldn't we report this?
Why don't you report all of us then?
Oh. we were going to do
the same thing. Sorry.
Boss. what are you planning to do now?
First.
I'm going to become
Lee Chung-won's vault keeper.
-What?
-His keeper?
Right.
You need the vault's key
to steal that fund.
But would Lee Chung-won
give you that position?
I'll make sure he has no other choice.
Let's go meet President Seo first.
Go and look for him.
-Yes. sir.
MAIL ARRIVAL NOTICE
What is it?
His card statement.
But there aren't any recent transactions.
He uses his card for everything.
I can tell what's going on.
What do you mean?
It's just like me.
I can't use my card either.
Can't you track his location or anything?
I can't. His phone is turned off.
What? He really is doing
the exact same thing I'm doing.
I can't turn on my phone either.
I just leave it somewhere warm
and use it to iron my clothes.
Good for you.
Wait.
President Seo went on a trip abroad?
I don't know.
He just sent a text
saying he's going overseas.
He betrayed us.
Traveling abroad
after the mess he created?
Just forget him.
We've decided to side
with the new president now.
so please put in a good word for us
with President Park.
You can rely on me.
I'm Hae-kang's right-hand man.
Is that so?
Would you like to have anything else?
Then can I order
another large tea?
You might feel sick
from a blood sugar spike.
Drink some water. Water. please.
Get us a big cup of water.
Please give us another big cup of tea.
-This too.
-Rice cakes.
More rice cakes too!
-President Seo?
-Yes.
What kind of work did he normally do here?
I'd like to learn what he did
and think about what to do
as the president--
Geez.
Just thinking about that asshole
makes my blood pressure rise
and gives me a headache.
He was acting as though
he were True Value's king…
King?
If I wrote down
every terrible thing he did.
there would be enough
for a full-length novel.
I'm not even sure where I should start.
Right. The most ridiculous one.
He bought water with the maintenance fees.
He ordered water every month
with the fees.
and when they were delivered
to the office.
the security guards
brought them to his house.
To his house?
Seriously.
it's not like water costs a fortune.
How cheap is that?
And does he think the guards
are his errand boys?
He orders them around.
His abuse of power is on another level.
And you know what's really funny?
Did you know that the cleaning staff
have been growing gardens on the rooftops?
No. There are gardens on the rooftops?
At first. I thought
they were just doing that as a hobby.
so I was going to turn a blind eye.
-But…
-Yes?
It turns out that they were delivering
all the vegetables from their gardens
to President Seo's house.
He didn't even let them use pesticides
because he wanted
to eat organic vegetables.
And the cleaning staff were too scared
of getting fired to protest.
They were farming
on top of all the cleaning work.
How can we call him human?
But you didn't say anything
when he was doing all that?
Why wouldn't I?
I'm Jang Suk-jin. you know.
Of course. I said something.
But that bastard didn't even blink an eye.
I could talk about this endlessly.
But do you know the worst thing
about President Seo?
He opposes every single thing
that the residents request or suggest.
2021. RESIDENTS' ASSOCIATION MEETING
Why do they keep refusing
to do the repairs?
It seems like the construction company
thinks we're pushovers.
We have to do something about this.
don't you think?
-Right.
-He's right.
I understand what you mean.
but we're up against a large company.
Can you guarantee
that we'll win a lawsuit against them?
And if word spreads
about our apartments having defects.
property values will drop.
Will you be okay with that?
A new seafood stew place opened nearby.
I'll give you a detailed explanation
over dinner there later.
So please. sit down.
In any case.
President Seo was a pro
at stopping anyone from filing a lawsuit.
And he harassed all the building reps
who had any complaints
and made them all give up
and move away in the end.
Then he placed his own people
in those empty seats.
He's a filthy fraud.
Just thinking about him
makes my blood boil.
He stopped the lawsuits
against Lee Chung-won's companies
and protected his money.
My keeper only has one job.
To keep my money safe.
I get what I have to do.
but will that be enough
to become one of his men?
I need something with real impact.
Something big.
Hello. ma'am.
Hello.
Were you buying groceries?
Yes.
We have business in Complex 2.
so excuse us.
Bye. Take care. ma'am.
She's so cold.
Well. I'm the one at fault.
Do I have to sleep
at Yeong-ju's again tonight?
Wait!
Were you out?
I went to the supermarket.
I got some boneless mackerel.
Mr. Hwang said it's hard to debone fish
because of his eyesight.
Who's Mr. Hwang?
The man you call the Lizard
and treat harshly.
You should've told Big Guy
to run errands like that.
He said something about boneless fish
not being real fish.
so he can't feed it to the kid.
He has some weird philosophy about it.
Big Guy has some serious opinions
when it comes to food.
Life isn't that complicated though.
We're just paying for convenience.
What's the big deal?
Are you okay?
Excuse me.
The elevator in Building 114 is broken.
The president's in here.
Please take care of this quickly.
Just a moment. ma'am.
That startled me.
I heard the elevators
are always breaking down.
You're the president.
Can't you take care of this?
You could just replace them all.
The long-term repair reserve fund
shouldn't be used so rashly.
Rashly?
You're resolving
an inconvenience with money.
Imagine having to use the stairs
every day instead.
Everyone will be demanding
that the fund be used.
Koreans can't stand any inconvenience.
They'll gladly pay
to make life more convenient.
They buy convenience.
like this boneless mackerel.
It's working now.
Let's go.
RESIDENTS' ASSOCIATION MEETING
Thank you for your suggestions.
To summarize.
replacing the equipment
in the community center gym.
toys for the kids cafe.
a donation to the senior center.
and repainting the exterior walls.
Yes. those are the main suggestions.
All right.
The suggestions you've made
are about making a better environment
and improving resident services here.
I also believe
all of these things are necessary.
But to resolve all these problems.
you know we need money. don't you?
It all requires money.
Money's the problem.
That is why I'm suggesting
a 100% increase in the reserve fund
for the present and future
of our apartment complex.
What? 100%?
100%?
Isn't 100% too much?
What? A 100% increase?
What's gotten into him?
What the heck is he thinking?
That took quite a surprising turn.
It does make me look forward
to the next episode.
Yes. go on.
Can't we cover
all the proposals from today
with the reserve fund
that we already have right now?
This apartment complex
is nearly ten years old now.
More and more repairs will be needed.
If we keep using
the reserve fund every time.
we won't have anything left.
To invest in improving
our living environment
and carry out future repair plans.
an increase in the reserve fund fee
is inevitable.
Excuse me.
I get all that.
but if you're going to increase the fee.
-you should do it gradually.
-Exactly.
You can't just increase it
by 100% so suddenly.
-That's a bit too much.
-Yeah.
Our apartment complex
has never raised the fee
since it was occupied.
If you factor in inflation.
the amount hasn't changed on paper.
but its real value
has been decreasing every year.
To put it simply.
you've been getting a discount
on the fee every year.
Well. you're not wrong.
but still…
We live in a large apartment complex.
Even a small repair
would be a huge project.
With the reserve fund we have now.
we won't be fully prepared
for future maintenance.
But nothing is that urgent right now.
A 100% increase is too much.
That's what I'm saying.
But President Park does have a point.
There are apartment complexes
similar to ours.
but they have much higher fees.
-Yeah.
-Right.
I agree as well.
More and more problems
will come up as time passes.
so it won't be a bad idea
to prepare in advance.
-Right?
-Yes.
You're right.
If it's never been increased before.
I guess it's about time.
Prices have gone up a lot over the years.
Still. I believe
a 100% increase is too much.
Right. I understand
your reason for opposing.
That's why I'd like to hold
a residents' vote this weekend.
A residents' vote. That's a good idea.
He's forward-thinking.
But do you really agree
to raising the reserve fund fee?
Of course not!
Then why?
We need to get on his good side.
We have to show him
that we're all on his side
to win some brownie points.
But what if he really increases the fee?
It's a 100% increase.
He can't. We're doing a vote.
The residents aren't crazy.
Why would they agree to that?
Then we just have to pretend
to support his proposal.
-then vote against it.
-That's right.
A proposal to raise
the reserve fund fee by 100%?
Is this the plan you prepared?
A meaningless vote?
Boss. this really doesn't make any sense.
It's impossible.
It's the cost of a whole chicken
plus cheese balls.
It's way too much.
Just wait.
More than half the residents
will vote yes in the end.
When are you coming home?
I'll come when I come.
You brat.
I told you not to wear this.
-You're wearing it again?
-Mom. there are people here.
What's going on?
What? Did it just stop?
Is this working? Hello?
Mr. Choi!
The elevator stopped!
ELEVATOR UNDER MAINTENANCE
Why is it so hard
just to smoke a cigarette?
Mom. my legs hurt. Carry me.
My legs hurt too.
Carry me!
We're late. Come on.
-I'll be late for kindergarten!
-All right.
There it is. Oh. hello.
I can't believe this!
-Why's it like this every day?
-You're so fast.
Yes. Building 107? We're so sorry.
We're checking right now.
Yes. the repair company is on its way.
Building 212 too?
If you can wait just a moment…
It's the first time
so many have broken down at once.
Is the repair company still not answering?
-Call them again.
-Okay.
We'll do our best
to take care of this issue
as soon as possible.
-Come on.
-When?
Everyone. we'll be able to take care
of this issue faster
if you all head back first.
-Do something about the elevators.
-Everyone.
-Please.
-How will you take care of this?
Are you even doing your jobs?
We live on the 28th floor.
Can you fix it before my kid comes home?
Everyone. I'm a resident here as well.
I had to walk too.
If you give us time.
we'll handle this as soon as possible.
Mr. Choi. let's call an emergency meeting.
Yes. sir.
That's not the problem right now.
How will we go upstairs?
RESIDENTS' ASSOCIATION
ELEVATOR BREAKDOWN RESPONSE MEETING
How will you take care of this?
Everyone. please calm down.
Let's hear from our president first.
To tell you the truth.
because of a strike
at the factory overseas.
they say it'll take a year
for the parts to arrive.
-How can we wait a year?
-That makes no sense!
How can we wait an entire year?
Do something. President Park!
We're checking with companies in Korea
to see if anyone has the parts.
so let's wait a bit longer.
You're always just asking us to wait.
-How long do we have to wait?
-Right?
It might be fine
for those on the lower floors.
but people living on higher floors
can't keep enduring this.
This is ridiculous!
My mother will collapse
climbing the stairs!
That is why
I am proposing
to replace all the elevators
to prevent the continuous breakdowns
and any future safety issues.
I can't believe this.
-That's easier said than done.
-Excuse me…
-It takes time and money.
-So…
That would cost a fortune.
How would you pay for that?
Is it possible
with the current reserve fund?
You're right.
Our reserve fund isn't enough.
We currently have
about 17 billion in the fund.
but we'd need approximately 20 billion
to replace the elevators
in every building.
Twenty billion?
Oh my gosh.
-Then we'd have to pay for the rest.
-President Park.
You don't seem to be aware of this.
but the elevators
have been breaking down for a long time.
It's been like this
ever since we first moved here.
-Exactly.
-Right.
We should really just
file a lawsuit this time.
Let's sue the company!
We should!
A lawsuit?
The defect repair period is already over.
I know it's upsetting.
but you should've done it sooner.
You stayed quiet until now.
but you blame the company
after the defect repair period is over?
That would only look
like you're throwing a fit.
What's more.
our opponent is a large company.
They'll hire
the best law firm in Korea to fight us.
And if we lose that fight.
we'll all have to bear
the enormous cost of that lawsuit.
Are you willing to take that risk?
-I have a headache.
-Then…
what are you suggesting?
I am sincerely urging you
to understand that an increase
in the reserve fund fee is inevitable.
That damn reserve fund…
We have to pay more?
Everyone. will you buy convenience
for the cost of one chicken?
Or will you keep living in fear.
riding an elevator
that could break down at any moment?
Your choice
will change your future.
I'm just going to vote yes.
It's not like the reserve fund
is going to disappear.
It's going back
into the apartment complex.
No. I can't deliver it on foot.
I'm on the first floor. Please come down.
It's Unit 2802.
Thank you.
I'm getting delivery
because I don't want to cook.
but this is going to kill my knees.
Whatever. I'm just going to vote yes.
How can the elderly live like this?
-My goodness…
-Just a moment.
Mother. let's get some rest here.
Gosh. my knees.
Money isn't the problem right now.
Be careful.
Did you hear they're doubling
the reserve fund fee?
Yeah.
Double the fee would be tough.
We're only renting.
Even if we pay it
and they replace the elevators.
we can get all the fees back
when we move out.
We have nothing to lose.
Are you happy?
Are you happy that we're renting?
Yeah. I am.
Why did the elevators have to break down
right after President Park got elected?
Those damn elevators.
He could become a lame duck at this rate.
What time is it?
Gosh. Is the vote closed now?
It's 6:30.
The vote closed at 6:00.
The results should've
been out immediately.
Why aren't they announcing it?
I'll go to the office myself and check…
This is the management office.
We'll announce the results
of the vote on increasing
the long-term repair reserve fund fee.
Of the 7.237 households
that participated in the vote.
52.7% were in favor.
-and 47.3% were against.
-We did it.
The proposal to increase the fee
has been approved.
Double the reserve fund!
Wow!
Double the reserve fund fee!
The increased
long-term repair reserve fund fee
will be reflected in the maintenance fees
starting this month.
We kindly ask
for your support and cooperation.
-Thank you.
-Park Hae-kang is amazing.
He really is quite the talent.
He really increased the reserve fund fee.
It seems…
I've gotten
a much better replacement.
Sorry for asking to meet
at such a late hour.
All the management companies
are yours. aren't they?
Oh. I was trying
not to make it so obvious.
Could you tell?
Call the elevator repair company.
Why?
I need to stop the elevators.
I'm different from President Seo.
Just keeping the money is no fun.
I told you.
just keeping it is hard enough.
I'd like to increase it.
not just protect it.
My money?
I did as you asked. Mr. Park.
But isn't this a huge gamble?
If it is. what would you bet on?
I don't bet anything
on something I'm not certain of.
Gambling
is what desperate people do.
You must be quite anxious.
You're more of a coward than I thought.
I don't start any games
that I'm not confident in.
You're very cool.
Why does Park Hae-kang
keep making my heart flutter?
This is bad.
Oh. right.
I have to do what he asked.
I already called the company.
They'll get the elevators
working again tonight.
But…
the residents won't just sit still
if you don't replace them.
Park Hae-kang said we'd need 20 billion.
so they'll wait
until it reaches that amount.
And after that.
we can just give another reason
to postpone it.
People forget things easily.
Yes. sir.
-There's something to report.
-Go on.
The man Park Hae-kang was meeting
was an official in the police.
Chief of Investigation. Son Dae-un.
He was the one who busted
Park's gambling den in Gangnam.
Then why would they meet up secretly?
It seems Chief Son
is holding Park Yong-man.
the former Oasis Gang boss. hostage.
He took Park Hae-kang in.
Park Yong-man is currently being held
at a detention center.
So that's why Park Hae-kang needed money.
To get his old boss out.
But sir.
Chief Son is connected
to the commissioner.
The commissioner?
The commissioner who's desperate
to join our One Club?
Yes. that's right.
Things are getting very interesting.
Mr. Kim.
We're going to get
double the reserve fund fees now.
Then there's another matter
to take care of.
Let's leave after just five more minutes.
What on earth is President Park thinking?
Could he…
be aware that we don't have the fund?
No. He could never tell from the papers.
Oh dear.
You're working late.
Ha-jeong. can I talk to you for a moment?
Mr. Choi. sit down.
We're a family.
Come on. Sit.
What is this about?
We're working on the elevator issue…
It's not about that.
Sir…
What is it?
I'd like to come clean
about something to you too.
I really like the ledger
that you organized.
Ms. Kang.
Even to me. it seems flawless.
It's me.
The guy who's taking the reserve fund.
You're making me embarrassed
with that reaction.
I'm not here to startle you.
I'm sorry if I shocked you.
The thing is.
I love the way you work. Ms. Kang.
But I heard you wanted to quit.
Was there anything that displeased you?
Was the pay too small?
No. it's nothing like that.
Or…
how about joining
Taesan Construction's finance team?
It's a better workplace than this.
and you can proudly tell your family
it's a large company.
What do you say?
Ms. Kang.
I'm offering you a job right now.
I'll give you twice your current salary.
Why aren't you answering?
He's asking you a question.
I'M SORRY. HA-JEONG
So you're supposed to draw your family?
Yes.
Let's see…
Why have you been sighing all day?
You're a young lady
with a whole future ahead of you.
That future has already
turned into a tangled mess.
You said you're a professional.
You should stick to your role
and help your kid with his homework.
Sometimes. moms can be depressed too.
You and that smart mouth of yours…
Ta-da. It's Dad. Park Hae-kang.
It looks just like him. right?
Isn't Park Hae-kang
a bit more handsome than that?
Do you really have to correct him
even when you're depressed?
Facts are important
to seven-year-olds. you know.
Geez.
You know
I can't stand people being bad at stuff.
Let's do your homework based on facts.
Okay.
What color should we use?
But aren't you going home? It's past 6:00.
I'm working overtime today.
Overtime?
Mr. Park makes you work overtime?
That brat.
Just report him to the Ministry of Labor.
No. this is voluntary overtime.
You don't even like your job.
What do you mean. "voluntary overtime"?
If you're going to keep sighing.
just go home.
Or at least tell me what's going on.
I just have something on my mind.
Uncle Big Guy…
I'm thinking of transferring
to a place with a higher salary.
You…
should start studying again.
Quit everything else
and focus on your studies.
I'll do whatever it takes to support you.
Ha-jeong.
just go live your own life.
Stop worrying about mine.
How can you say that to me?
I can.
I have to.
Just please stop wasting your own life
to support mine.
That's enough.
Get back to your studies.
You should take the bar exam again.
I'll handle this on my own.
Ha-ri!
I'm really sorry I lied to you.
but I'm not quitting this gig.
What?
Ha-jeong.
I've already failed.
So you should accept that too.
Someone told me
that there are things you see
only after you fail.
And what I saw…
is you.
I saw your life
that's been tied down by me.
-Ha-ri. I--
-I'm grateful.
I'm really grateful for the youth
that you wasted because of me.
And I'm really sorry.
I'm going to start over.
I'll achieve my dream on my own now.
Why am I even here?
Why do you keep crying?
The debt collectors
were pressuring me today.
Don't worry about me and go home.
Please let me stay the night.
Boss. why are you…
Ms. Kang. why are you…
What?
Everyone. get up!
Come out here!
-What?
-What is it?
Everyone. come out here!
What?
-What is it?
-Did you two…
-What?
What is it?
I'll pretend I didn't see that.
-No. it's not like that.
-You got the wrong idea.
What's going on?
What is it?
Ms. Kang just came out of the bedroom.
What's wrong with that?
They're both young.
People had children even during wars.
-What are you saying?
-Children?
Boss. you can tell us the truth.
You really…
No. we were the ones who were clueless.
We'll spend the night
somewhere else twice a week!
-All of you. stop it!
-You brat…
From an intermittent family
to a real family…
A love story?
-No. a soap opera!
-A soap opera!
Let's give them some privacy today!
-All right.
-Come on. Let's go.
I had no idea.
What?
-Why…
-Bye. then.
What's with you guys?
We'll be back later.
Hit the elevator button.
Come here.
Gosh.
Gentlemen. have some snacks.
Gather round.
That must be tasty.
Great timing. I was hungry.
Come on.
All right.
I bought these from a restaurant
going viral on social media.
I waited two hours.
It was worth the wait.
Let me pack any leftovers
so I can give them to my wife.
You have to be good to your wife
when you're old.
She's your retirement plan.
You must be in a good mood today.
I am.
But it's not because of you.
You can listen while you eat.
After a long wait.
our Oman New Town project
is back on track.
Let's drink to that.
-Congratulations.
-Cheers!
As promised.
money will start pouring
into your pockets now.
So who should you be good to?
Your retirement
isn't secured by a wife
who can cheat on you anytime.
It's secured by money.
I'll be the one
taking care of your future now.
so you should be good to me.
Don't you think?
Right. You're better than my own son.
You did a great job.
Isn't it nice to have
construction resume again?
Yes. Very nice.
Getting everything handed to you.
You're very lucky to have all that
without lifting a finger.
-Come on.
-Eat up. everyone.
Sir.
Commissioner Kwak Ju-gwon is here.
What is this?
I got these valuable ginseng roots
especially for you.
hoping they'll help restore your energy.
Ginseng doesn't agree with me.
I have too much heat in my body.
You can have them.
Pardon?
By the way.
how's the ten billion won coming along?
Yes. well…
My men are getting it prepared.
Your men? Not yourself?
Well.
there are friends helping me.
So you're extorting it.
Oh. goodness.
Extorting?
I'm just getting help.
I built a lot of connections
during my years as a cop.
And which of those connections
is getting you ten billion won?
It's a guy who used to run a gambling den.
He's a pro when it comes to getting money.
A guy who ran a gambling den?
Yes.
His name's Park Hae-kang.
-Park Hoe-kwang?
-No.
Hae-kang.
-Park Hae-kang?
-Yes.
How do you know such a competent guy?
Can you introduce me to him later?
Sure. I will.
I'll leave this with you.
President Park.
The 100% increase in the reserve fund fee.
I was really touched by what you achieved.
Can I give you a hug?
You're making my heart pound these days.
I'm so excited.
Is it your first time in a penthouse?
It's nothing special.
The ceiling's high.
but besides that.
it's no different from other houses.
So have I proven that I'm better
than President Seo?
Of course.
Thinking back now.
President Seo was really useless.
Very incompetent.
I despise incompetent people the most.
Then will you let me be the keeper
of your vault?
You are the perfect man
to take on that position.
I'll count on you.
I believe we'll make a great team.
Don't you agree?
I do feel bad putting you to work
as soon as you've joined me
without even a honeymoon period.
but I have an urgent favor to ask you.
Sure.
It's nothing difficult.
Just take some money from Mr. Kim
and deliver it to an apartment complex
in Gunam City.
It's actually another complex
that I'm skimming from.
I'm just putting back the money
I took out of there.
There's going to be an audit soon.
so I'll get it back afterward.
I understand.
This is actually
what President Seo used to do.
So think of this as training for the job.
I'm counting on you.
-Hey. Gyeong-nam.
-Boss.
We tracked President Seo's whereabouts.
and the last signal from his phone
came from Taegowon.
-Taegowon?
-Yes.
Je-gil hacked the security cams there.
but he didn't ever see him
leave the premises.
It seems like President Seo was taken out.
And…
his entire family disappeared as well.
-Disappeared?
-Yes.
Their belongings are still there.
but his family's gone.
It's like someone just erased them.
Boss.
becoming Lee Chung-won's vault keeper
is dangerous.
Just stop digging
into President Seo for now.
All right.
Taegowon…
KIM HONG-HYEON
LEE JAE-GU
SEO GANG-WON
There are names for each of the trees.
What are they?
They're people who sacrificed themselves
for Taegowon.
So they're like commemorative trees.
This is ten billion.
I can't get him released.
But I'll let him get treatment outside.
Anything else
will be discussed
after you bring the money.
MR. SON. SEOUL POLICE CHIEF
Yes?
Hey. Mr. Park.
Did you know
Park Yong-man was terminally ill?
Hey. you can't just stop like that!
What did you just say?
You didn't know?
They say it's pancreatic cancer.
He has about three months left.
So…
you'd better hurry
if you don't want him to die in there.
Get the ten billion.
So the commissioner attacked Park Hae-kang
to give me ten billion won.
and that's why Park Hae-kang
was trying to take ten billion
from the reserve fund
in my apartment complex?
Mr. Kim.
I think I could get
the competent Park Hae-kang for free.
Do you trust Park Hae-kang?
I'm going to do one last test…
to see if I can trust him or not.
I'm bringing over the ten billion.
so release him.
Right now!
THE APARTMENT JOB
Hey. did you know that there are people
using our community sauna for free?
-We use our cards to enter.
-Unbelievable.
You should see this.
A complaint about people
using our facilities.
-They want a facial recognition system.
-I can't do this any longer.
Use the reserve fund?
-No.
We need to find the people
and give them a warning.
It's a rental unit.
"Reveal the rental units." Nonsense.
The rental units are the problem.
-Conflict.
-Ms. Kang. can you work overtime today?
Why Park Hae-kang?
Park Hae-kang can see the bigger picture.
Can you do something for me?
And when it's over.
I'll give you the ten billion.
You'd better hurry.
because that ten billion you want
is on borrowed time too.
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org